Then you select template. And in the
storage configuration, select also
volume disk. I've also posted a runpod
template link in my Discord with my free
master comfy UI workflow. After you done
these easy steps, you hit deploy and
everything is already on the pod. You
just have to wait a few minutes after
you click deploy because the template is
booting and pulling the docker image. On
the pod is already the Z image turbo
model, the VAEs, and the encoders, and
the decoders, and so on. You don't have
to download anything anymore. The only
thing that's not on there is your
character Laura. To add your Laura it's
really easy. Just open the Jupiter
notebook on the port 888 and navigate to
Laura.